A Finding Aid to the Colin de Land Collection, 1968-2008, bulk 1980-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.delacoli
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; Series 1; 12 Linear feet Box 1-12
  - Snapshots, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; 1.1
    - Christian Philipp Muller Birthday, 1997; Includes negatives only. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Bernadette Corporation and F.C. Gundlach Opening, 1997 January (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, F.C. Gundlach, Jack Pierson, Peter Fend, Colin de Land’s aunt Irene, Dr. Hamada, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, [Chivas Clem?], Carol Greene, David Karlin, Anastasie Croy, Trudie Reiss, Julian LaVerdiere, and Frank Schroder.
    - Frank Schroder, 1997 February (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Frank Schroder. Also includes Frank Schroder's Crowd of Women installation at an unidentified gallery.
    - Pat Hearn Benefit, 1997 February (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn Emergency Art Benefit at Pat Hearn Art Gallery, Colin de Land, Brice Marden, Chivas Clem, Dennis Balk, Moyra Davey, Paul Morris, Leslie Nolan, Rosalie Knox, Frank Schroder, Sam Grubman, Craig Wadlin, Anastasie Croy, and Brigid Berlin.
    - Various Subjects, 1997 February (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Envelope says, PH, Complete Set BCorp Show, but includes photos of Pat Hearn, Frank Schroder, Craig Wadlin, Isa Genzken. Negatives include Bernadette Corporation photographs.
    - New York Outing, 1997 March (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Dennis Balk, Paul Morris, David Karlin, John Waters, Daniel McDonald, Peter Fend, Sam Grubman, artwork by Dennis Balk, New York street scenes.
    - Various Subjects, 1997 March (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, John Waters, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, office of Drs. Mills and Scarpinato, artwork by Dennis Balk and Roy Arden.
    - Norman Installation, Pierson, 1997 March (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Includes photos of installation of Nils Norman exhibition Social Surplus (1997) at American Fine Arts, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Nils Norman, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Jack Pierson, and Cris Moor.
    - Norman Opening, Easter, 1997 March (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Nils Norman, Jackie McAllister, Barbara Morse, Ira Richer, Margaret Deluccia, David Karlin, Daniel McDonald, Peter Fend, Carol Greene, Craig Wadlin, Cris Moor, Anastasie Croy, and Julian LaVerdiere.
    - Easter at Maxims and Various, 1997 March (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Matthew Marks, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Tom Burr, Jack Pierson, Craig Wadlin, Cris Moor, Daniel McDonald, Chivas Clem, Tom Healy, Massimo Audiello, Gillian Haratani, Barbara Morse, Cathy Torsney, [Marion Hearn?], Stuart Regen, artwork by Nils Norman, rephotographed Cris Moor magazine tearsheets.
    - Cape Cod and Various, circa April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, [Winnie Lawless?], [Frank Darcy?], Christine Tsvetanov, Craig Wadlin, Ania Corcilius, Ed Schott, drawings by Mark Dion, artwork by Mariko Mori.
    - Party, circa April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Tom Healy, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Elizabeth Peyton, Olivier Mosset, Rirkrit Tiravanija, and Colin de Land.
    - Easter, 1997 April (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
      Includes photos of Easter outing in Central Park and at Maxim’s restaurant with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, Cathy Torsney, Jack Pierson, Cris Moor, Tom Burr, Moyra Davey, Jason Simon, Craig Wadlin, [Marion Hearn?], Massimo Adiello, Chivas Clem.
    - Tom Burr, Stainless, 1997 April (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Includes negatives only of photos of Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Tom Burr, Christine Tsvetanov, Carey Hirvonen, and the American Fine Arts office. Photos by Craig Wadlin, taken during installation.
    - Tom Burr, Stainless, 1997 April (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Tom Burr exhibition Stainless (1997) at American Fine Arts, Colin de Land, Jack Pierson, Tom Burr, Christine Tsvetanov, Cathy Torsney, Elizabeth Peyton, Craig Wadlin, Liz-and-Val, Rosalie Knox, David Karlin, Pat Hearn, Ira Richer, [Angela Cumberich?], Margaret Deluccia, and Daniel McDonald.
    - John Waters Pink Flamingos Re-opening, 1997 April 7 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of opening events for reissue of Pink Flamingos, with John Waters, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Walter Hopps, Caroline Huber Hopps, Jean Stein, Daniel McDonald, David Karlin, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani.
    - Vault Flood, Brunch at America, 60s Show, 1997 April 13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Gillian Haratani, Dennis Balk, Craig Wadlin, Cris Moor, David Karlin, Daniel McDonald, rephotographed Pat Hearn spread in Vogue, vault flood.
    - Brunch at America, 60s Show, 1997 April 13 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of brunch at America restaurant and a vintage pop culture fair, with Colin de Land with Abraham Lincoln and George Washington impersonators, Pat Hearn, Matthew Marks, Sam Grubman, Jack Pierson, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Dennis Balk, Gillian Haratani, Chivas Clem, Cris Moor, and rephotographed photos of models and movie posters.
    - Burr Show, Misc. Rephotographs, 1997 April-June (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, rephotographed newspapers and magazines, Tom Burr exhibition Stainless (1997), artwork by Roy Arden and Edward Schott.
    - Christine Tsvetanov Wedding, Gramercy Art Fair, 1997 May (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair, Matthew Marks, Peter Fend, Georg Kargl, Gillian Haratani, Andrea Fraser, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Colin de Land with antler necklace, Picasso’s Bust of Sylvette in Greenwich Village, Karen Hallock, Pat Hearn, David Karlin, wedding of Christine Tsvetanov and Todd Parkin, with guests including John Waters, Tom Burr.
    - Chicago Art Fair, Christine Tsvetanov Wedding, 1997 May (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of Christine Tsvetanov’s wedding reception with, Christine Tsvetanov, Todd Parkin, Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Tom Burr, Gillian Haratani, Cris Moor, David Karlin. Also includes Chicago Art Fair, artwork by Dan Graham, Roy Lichtenstein, and Renee Green's Simulated Vinyl Diary.
    - Dion at the Wexner Center, 1997 May (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion exhibition Cabinet of Curiosities for the Wexner Center for the Arts, Columbus, Ohio. Folder 16 also includes Colin de Land, Barbara and Howard Morse, Mark Dion, Bob Braine, Alexis Rockman, Moyra Davey, Jason Phillips, American Fine Arts façade, vault flooding.
    - Christine Tsvetanov Wedding, Venice, 1997 May-June (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of wedding of Christine Tsvetanov and Todd Parkin, Pat Hearn, John Waters, Daniel McDonald, Cris Moor, David Karlin, Craig Wadlin, Andrea Fraser, Ira Richer, Tom Burr, Gillian Haratani, Margaret Deluccia, Christian Philipp Muller, artwork by Mark Dion.
    - Venice Biennale, Karaoke, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion, Barbara Morse, David Karlin, Ira Richer, Dan Graham, Almine Rech, Peter Fend, Julian Schnabel at the Venice Biennale (or Documenta X); Christian Philipp Muller at Documenta X in Kassel, Germany. Also includes Takahiro Imamura, Christine Tsvetanov, Daniel McDonald, Pat Hearn, John Waters, Craig Wadlin, [Brigid Berlin?] in New York.
    - Venice Biennale, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 19-22)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion installation/archeological dig, Colin de Land, Peter Fend, Orlan, Howard Morse, Barbara Morse, J. Morgan Puett, Andrea Fraser, Nils Norman, Julian Schnabel, Lisa Spellman; artwork by Mariko Mori, Jessica Stockholder, Julian Schnabel, Jeff Koons, Tracey Moffet, Jason Rhoades; photographed correspondence between Colin de Land and Roy Arden regarding Arden leaving American Fine Arts. Folder 20 also includes Daniel McDonald with black eye at American Fine Arts.
    - Basel, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Includes photos taken at the Basel Art Fair, with Colin de Land and artwork by Mark Dion, Christian Philipp Muller, Vibeke Tandberg, Vassili Balatsos, and Mary Heilmann.
    - Documenta X, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 24-26)
      Includes photos of Documenta X in Kassel, Germany, with Christian Philipp Muller, Esther Friedman, Frank Schroder, Eva and Adele, Christian Nagel, artwork by Claes Oldenburg, Pawel Althamer, Carsten Holler and Rosemarie Trockel, Catherine Beaugrand, and Mariella Mosle.
    - Berlin, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Esther Friedman, artwork by Martin Kippenberger and Chuck Close, Mondo Morricone.
    - Hamburg and Berlin, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Esther Friedman, Berlin street scenes, Paris Bar with artwork by J. Saint Bernard, Mark Dion exhibition (likely The Museum of Natural History and Other Fictions at Kunstverein, Hamburg).
    - Mark Dion Exhibition, Hamburg, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Includes installation shots of Mark Dion exhibition (likely The Museum of Natural History and Other Fictions at Kunstverein, Hamburg), with photos of large dinner after the opening reception with Colin de Land and Mark Dion. Also includes photos of F.C. Gundlach and rephotographed photos.
    - Hamburg, F.C. Gundlach, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, F. C. Gundlach, and Esther Friedman at the home of F.C. Gundlach, Galerie Der Gegenwart, artwork by Louise Lawler and Jeff Koons.
    - Hamburg and American Fine Arts, 1997 June (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land at the Hamburg airport. Also includes photos taken at American Fine Arts, including of Ania Concilius and Gillian Haratani, plus a photo of Craig Wadlin in an unknown location. With photos of flooding behind American Fine Arts and water damage to artwork, [Roy Arden?] in a taxi driven by a clown.
    - Santa Fe, Cape Cod, 1997 July (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Cris Moor, Lisa Spellman, Francesco Bonami in Santa Fe for group exhibition at SITE Santa Fe, TRUCE: Echoes of Art in an Age of Endless Conclusions (1997); artwork by Cris Moor, Dan Graham, and Tom Burr. Also includes photos taken in Cape Cod, with Pat Hearn and Chandler Hearn.
    - Cape Cod, New York, 1997 July; 1998 December (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Includes July 1997 photos from Cape Cod of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Pat de Groot, Jack Pierson, Rosalie Knox with a puppy, and rephotographed newspaper stories about the Gianni Versace murder. Envelope also includes photos from December 1998 of Mark Dion, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, J. Morgan Puett, Cris Moor, Nils Norman, Christopher Sperandio, Jacqueline Humphries, and Peter Fend.
    - Various Subjects, Fall 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of book display with Jack Pierson book; Jack Pierson photographing Stella Tennant; Gillian Haratani, Colin de Land, Roy Arden, Margaret Dellucia, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, Alex Bag, damaged F.C. Gundlach prints; postcard for Andrea Fraser exhibition White People in West Africa 1989-1991 (1997); construction at American Fine Arts.
    - De Appel, 1997 September (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Anton and Anik Herberts, [Mark Dion installation?].
    - Gramercy International Contemporary Photography Fair, 1997 October (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of photos by Hans Namuth, Bob Jackson, and John Waters; Rave shampoo installation; Also includes photos of F. C. Gundlach, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, [Brigid Berlin?], Pat Hearn, and Colin de Land.
    - Gordon Matta Clark, circa November 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Envelope says S. Levine, Lawler, Lawson, Gordon Matta Clark, James Coleman, Acconci, Fisette, Melvin Ziegler, but packet includes only photos of Gordon Matta Clark split house. Includes additional negatives with no prints.
    - Chateau Marmont, Los Angeles, 1997 December (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair at Chateau Marmont, Los Angeles street scenes, Nuart theater marquee playing Cindy Sherman’s Office Killer, Christine Tsvetanov, Dennis Balk, David Karlin, artwork by Mark Dion.
    - De Land Family Christmas, Various, 1997 December (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of James Welling, Christian Philipp Muller, Pat Hearn in the hospital, Aleta Hamada, Dr. Hamada, Colin de Land’s aunt, Jack Pierson, Colin de Land, Takahiro Imamura, rephotographed documentation labeled Driver’s Revenge Refo.
    - Tom Burr Party, SoHo Grand Dinner, 1997 December (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of Takahiro Imamura, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Andrea Fraser, Colin de Land, Christian Philipp Muller, David Karlin, Pat Hearn, Sam Grubman, Massimo Audiello, Jack Pierson, Cathy Torsney, Dennis Balk, Tom Burr.
    - Paul Morris Christmas Party, New Years, 1997 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, David Karlin, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Takahiro Imamura, [Danette and Jean Seberg], Bruce Fuller, Massimo Audiello, computer screen with Colin de Land contact information. Includes photos of New Years at Indochine.
    - Portraits, Fall 1997-Winter 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Includes self portrait of Colin de Land in the elevator at John Waters' apartment and rephotographed portrait of Tom Healy and Paul Morris. Includes additional negatives with no prints.
    - Miami Gramercy, New Years, 1998 January; Includes negatives only. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Miami Gramercy, Cher at Bono's Funeral, 1998 January (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of the Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair in Miami at the Raleigh Hotel, with Daniel McDonald, Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman. Also includes photos of television screens with Sonny Bono’s funeral.
    - Sperandio and Grannan at AFA, Madrid, 1998 January-February (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of installation and opening of the exhibition The Bradford 100 (1998) by Christopher Sperandio and Simon Grennan at American Fine Arts, John Waters, Takahiro Imamura, Craig Wadlin, Rosalie Knox, Christian Nagel, Marta Cervera, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Frank Schroder, Daniel McDonald, Daniel Reich, Peter Fend, artwork by Jack Pierson.
    - Madrid, 1998 February (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
      Includes photos of Tom Burr exhibition The Medical Show (1998) at Galeria Marta Cervera; ARCO art fair; Christian Philipp Muller exhibition Naturalezas Muertas (1998) at Galeria Oliva Arauna; Colin de Land, Tom Burr, Marta Cervera, Barbara and Howard Morse, Tom Burr, Nancy and Joel Portnoy; artwork by Vik Munez and Francis Picabia.
    - Pierson Studio, 1998 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of artwork at Jack Pierson’s studio.
    - Schroder Opening, 1998 March 18 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Crowd of Women 1909-1959,The Collection of F. L. Schroder at AFA, Pat Hearn, Barbara and Howard Morse, Nancy Portnoy, and Daniel McDonald.
    - Various Subjects, 1998 March 25 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of Frank Schroder, Audiello Gallery opening, Patterson Beckwith, Pat Hearn, and Takahiro Imamura, vault.
    - Cape Cod, Easter, 1998 April (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Jack Pierson, and houses on Cape Cod.
    - American Fine Arts, 1998 April (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Includes Colin de Land self portrait with Society of the Spectacle by Guy Debord, rephotographed exhibition announcements, A.A. Bronson and Mark Krayenhoff van de Leur with work by Christian Philipp Muller.
    - Vault Flood, 1998 April 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Jack Pierson Exhibition Preview, AFA, 1998 April 17 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
      Includes photos of preview reception for Jack Pierson exhibition at AFA, with Roberta Smith, Peter Fend, Jack Pierson, [Nan Goldin?], Christine Tsvetanov, Rosalie Knox, Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land, Alex Katz, Jess Holzworth, Craig Wadlin, Takahiro Imamura, Tom Borgese, Red Ed. Folder 22 also includes Colin de Land at Gaiety Theater with Twirl Gogo, the AFA vault, Peter Fend installation of map.
    - Cape Cod, Garry Gross, 1998 April-May (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Includes photos of Moyra Davey, Jason Simon, Colin de Land, Jack Pierson, Garry Gross slides.
    - Various Subjects, 1998 May 9-20 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Peter Fend drawings, Marta Cervera, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Peter Fend, Jutta Koether, Friedrich Petzel, Craig Wadlin, Dennis Balk, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, Georg Kargl, Matthew Antezzo paintings, Andrea Rosen gallery closing on Prince Street.
    - Art Club 2000 Night of the Living Dead Author, 1998 May 14-21 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Art Club 2000 exhibition Night of the Living Dead Author (1998) with stretch limo, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Gillian Haratani, Craig Wadlin, Andrea Fraser, Takahiro Imamura, Colin de Land, Chelsea Ya' Later sign, zombie makeup session.
    - Key West and Exhibitions, 1998 June (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Jack Pierson, and Mary Heilmann in Key West, the Ernest Hemingway house; Rirkrit Tiravanija, Jess Holzworth, Ed Schott, Ellsworth Kelly exhibition at Matthew Marks Gallery, paintings by Vanessa Beecroft, opening of John Waters exhibition Marks at Gavin Brown’s Enterprise, model of Dan Graham artwork Swimmer.
    - Florida and Flooding in SoHo, 1998 June (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of Key West and Hollywood, Florida, Colin de Land, Dan Graham, Jeff Wall, Jess Holzworth, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, vault flood, SoHo floods viewed from Novecento restaurant, rephotographed portraits of Alanna Heiss.
    - Art Club 2000, Night of the Living Dead Author, 1998 June 12 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Includes photos of police officer cut outs in Night of the Living Dead Author installation by Art Club 2000 at American Fine Arts,with Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, Rosalie Knox, Takahiro Imamura.
    - Key West, Florida, 1998 June 14-17 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Jack Pierson, and Mary Heilmann on a boat.
    - John Waters Pecker Dinner, 1998 June-July (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Includes photos of John Waters, Christina Ricci, Brigid Berlin, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Dennis Balk, Daniel McDonald,[ Leslie?], Craig Wadlin, Christopher Sperandio at Time Warner store after MoMA meeting, [Louis Johnson?], Ken Saylor.
    - Mark Dion Artwork in Storage, circa August 1998 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion artwork in storage, with Colin de Land and Pat Hearn.
    - Various Subjects, circa August 1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Nan Goldin, Daniel McDonald, Moyra Davey, Jason Simon, Jack Pierson, Cris Moor, Craig Wadlin, Bruce Fuller.
    - Gallery Storage, 1998 August (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Takahiro Imamura, [Christine Tsvetanov], Jack Pierson, gallery storage space with artwork by John Dogg and other unidentified works of art.
    - Cape Cod, 1998 August (Box 7, Folder 36-39)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, David Karlin, Rosalie Knox, Nan Goldin, Craig Wadlin, [Marion Hearn?], Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Pat de Groot, Jack Pierson, John Waters, Mark Dion Flotsam and Jetsam fax.
    - Garry Gross Opening, 1998 September (Box 7, Folder 40)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Garry Gross, Brooke Shields, The Woman and the Child (1998) at American Fine Arts, with David Karlin, Spencer Sweeney, Jaiko Suzuki, Brian Degraw, Massimo Audiello, Brice Marden, Helen Marden, Rachel Harrison, Garry Gross, Christine Tsvetanov, Daniel McDonald, John Waters, Takahiro Imamura, Carol Greene, Jacqueline Humphries, Dennis Dermody, and Patricia Hearst.
    - American Fine Arts Renovation, 1998 September-October (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Includes photos of Margaret Deluccia, Peter Fend, Pat Hearn, Rosalie Knox, Gillian Haratani, Takahiro Imamura, Shikio Kozue, Colin de Land, Moyra Davey and daughter.
    - Garry Gross and John Knight Exhibitions, 1998 September-October (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of Christine Tsvetanov, Rosalie Knox, Cris Moor, Carol Greene, Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, Garry Gross, Julian LaVerdiere, Rachel Harrison, artwork by John Knight and Garry Gross, Brooke Shields: The Woman and the Child (1998).
    - Various Subjects, 1998 October (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land with head wound or blood makeup, Pat Hearn, Liz-and-Val, Patterson Beckwith, Takahiro Imamura, Alex Bag, John Waters at performance of I’m Still Here, Damnit! By Sandra Bernhard, street scenes with Broadway theater marquees, John Waters installation, artwork by Christian Philipp Muller.
    - Margaret Deluccia and Advertisments, 1998 October-November (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of Margaret Deluccia, Lizzi Bougatsos, and Cher advertisements.
    - Bill Owens, November 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Includes rephotographed Bill Owens prints and two photos from an opening reception.
    - John Waters Opening, 1998 November (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of Opening reception and dinner for John Waters exhibition Low Definition (1998), Johnny Depp, Vanessa Paradis, John Waters, Cindy Sherman, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Brigid Berlin, Takahiro Imamura, Daniel McDonald, Patterson Beckwith, David Karlin, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Jason Search, George Stoll, Alex Bag, Lizzi Bougatsos, Jess Holzworth, Spencer Sweeney, Julian LaVerdiere, Nancy Portnoy, Bruce Fuller, artwork by John Waters and John Knight.
    - Art Club 2000 Meeting and San Francisco, 1998 November (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, Alex Bag, Mark Dion, Gillian Haratani; Mark Dion exhibition at Yerba Buena Center for the Arts; Collection of Themistocles and Dare Michos.
    - San Francisco, 1998 November (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Gillian Haratani. Includes additional negatives with no prints.
    - American Fine Arts and Chateau Marmont, 1998 November-December (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Eva and Adele at John Waters exhibition Low Definition (1998) at American Fine Arts, Peter Fend, Mark Dion, Jessica Stockholder drawings documented before return to Jay Gorney gallery; Colin de Land, Shaun Caley Regen, [Ivy?] at Chateau Marmont.
    - Actress Concert, Dion, Chateau Marmont, 1998 December (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of concert by Actress (Lizzi Bougatsos, Amy Gartrell, Jess Holzworth, Hillary Smalls and Spencer Sweeney) at the Bowery Ballroom; Mark Dion, J. Morgan Puett, Peter Fend, Christine Tsvetanov, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Carol Greene, Daniel McDonald, Julian LaVerdiere, Takahiro Imamura at the opening of Mark Dion exhibition Loot, Trophies, Souvenirs, and White Elephants, Selected Works 1991-1998; Chateau Marmont.
    - Chateau Marmont, 1998 December (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Daniel’s brother, Sally McDonald, Esther Friedman, [Tara Donovan?], [Dannette?], [Stephen Prina?], artwork by Garry Gross, unidentified band.
    - Various Subjects, 1998 December-1999 January (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of Peter Fend, Daniel McDonald, note from Sam Taylor-Woods and Frieze cover, Christmas decorations.
    - American Fine Arts and Cape Cod, circa 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)